(Preparing for launch.)
(The first and second liquid fuel systems are ready.)
(T minus ten seconds.)
(Sound suppression water system activated.)
(Main engine ignition.)
(Three... two... one...)
(SRB ignition.)
(Lift off!)
ふわり 静寂 （しじま） をつらぬき
轻轻地 划破 寂静
空の 色が変わってゆく Daylight
天空的 颜色逐渐变成了 Daylight
憧れてきた 大圏 飛び立て
动身飞往 憧憬已久的 大气层
胸に湧き上がる 気持ち 最高？感動？ いつか 約束した軌跡 Satellite
涌上心头的 这个心情 惊讶？感动？ 抵达了 曾经约定的轨道 Satellite
舞い上がって今 展開 廻りはじめる
此刻 翩翩飞舞 展开双翼 开始公转
Jump ahead, go!
さあ！ここから星へ 繋ぐよ声を
来啊！从即刻起向繁星 发出连系彼此
どこまでも青く響く よろこび
响彻全宇宙的蔚蓝 喜悦之声
僕たちはここで 君と出会える
我们就在这里 正等待与你相会
満ち溢れる 期待
洋溢满心的 期待
到来 黎明 Swing-by! Starline's Day
(T plus one-hundred seconds; exceeding supersonic speed.)
(Okay. Engine position is looking good.)
(T plus one-hundred and twenty seconds; standing by for SRB burnout and jettison.)
(SRB jettisons confirmed.)
(T plus one-hundred and thirty seconds; we have an unknown MECO.)
(Main engine cut-off confirmed.)
聴こえるよ
我听得见哟
結び合う絆が照らす
彼此的牵绊所照耀的
地球の光
地球之光
さあ！ここから星へ 繋ごう夢を
来啊！从即刻起向繁星 述说连系彼此
いつでも確かめ合える かがやき
随时都可证实的梦想 光辉闪闪
新しい波で 君に届ける
凭借崭新的波浪 传达给你
切り開くよ 時代
即将开辟 新时代
共鳴 欣快 幸甚 連綿
共鸣 欣喜 幸甚 连绵
感応 広大 凡愛 悠遠
感应 宏大 凡爱 悠远
到来 黎明 Swing-by! Starline's Day
到来 黎明 Swing-by!Starline's Day
飛びこめ！ここまで！
立刻起飞！飞到这里！